<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">blmonopoly</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="confirm">OK</string>
    <!-- Launch Page -->
    <string name="start_game">START</string>
    
    <!-- Game page -->
    <string name="level">Level is</string>
    
    <!-- make friend -->
    <string name="make_friend_title">Make Friend</string>
    <string name="jouralist_baimugui">You are assigned to interview a killer who killed his father. You thought he is a perverted guy.
       But things turns out not quite the same as you think about. He is slient and honest. You are interested in him, and want to know
       what happened to him. So you keep in touch with him personally. </string>
    <string name="journalist_gaoyu">As a new journalist, you are introduced to one of the colleage. He is full of power on everything.
        You are talking happily with each other. You know that you can learn a lot from him. Just follow him, you will be able to 
        became a super journalist. </string>
    <string name="jouralist_majian">You are assigned to follow a drug case. In the dedicated place, you only see one guy stand there.
        The time passed, but no one else coming. You thought that maybe the intelligence is not correct. You come to talk the only 
        guy you see. He is very dignified. He thought you are a callboy. Ask your name, phone number and leave. </string>
    <string name="journalist_quanshui">You are assigned to interview a new pop star. He just annource to become a actor last week.
        He is so cute and quite like a girl. Most time, he still not able to answer the question well. But that is also attact you.
        Personally you also ask to get in touch with each other. </string>
    <string name="journalist_xitiao">You are assigned to interview the pop star who just win the second place for a charts. During the 
        interview you know that he has win the first place for 5 years before. Now he is so sad about the result. You give him some 
        encourage and comfort. And you invite him to have a drink together after the interview. </string>
    <string name="doctor_chenggu">He is coming to purpuit curing the neat freak. He wears the glove all the time. And do not touch 
        anything in the room. You are willing to be the physician in charge. You want to cure him very well. </string>
    <string name="doctor_heilai">In a doctor summit. You see someone who is much more slient than others. He did not say anything in
         the summit, and also not show any expression. You are curious what he is thinking about. So you went to talk with him. To your
         surprise, he talk to you much. And you leave the phone number and keep in touch. </string>
    <string name="doctor_gaochuan">A new graduated doctor join into your hospital. He is so charming and every nerse want to talk to 
        him. He is assigned to follow with you. So you get more chance to come together with him. You find it is a good thing, because 
        girls are followed you too because he is around you. </string>
    <string name="doctor_xiaoniaoyou">After you graudated from the university. You have long time not see the guy who are in the same 
        community with you during the university. It is happened that you see each other in the street, and went to drink together because 
        he is sad that day. You know that something happened to him. But you are not able to let him talk you the truth now. But you tell
         him to call you whenever he want someone to drink together. </string>
    <string name="doctor_shidai">He has the gunshot wounds. The men he owns are very nerious to ask for my help. You have the operation for 
        him. And he has no risk now. You know he is hooligan. But it looks he is handsome and tender. You want to know more, so talk to him. 
        And we know each other. </string>
    <string name="bar_shenwei">You are searching for a new bartender, and he comes. The excellent skill and handsome face attract you 
        immediately. You hire him and he begins to work in your bar.</string>
    <string name="bar_gaochuan">One night, two girls are contested a him. He is so optional. But no obvious like or not like. That attitude 
        make you feel a little angry and a little interested. So you went to talk to him. And then you two become friends. </string>
    <string name="bar_xitiao">One day, a group of guys are drinking in your bar. He is so outstanding from them due to the beautiful face 
        and special ethos. He drunk and keep talking something. Looks very funny. You keep him in the bar until he is sober up.</string>
    <string name="bar_shouye">You are searching for someone to play the paino in your bar. He comes. He plays very well. And also he is 
        able to help much more than playing paino. He know the account, the also can help on serving. You are quite happy that he can 
        work in your bar. </string>
    <string name="bar_hezhi">He always drinks in your bar. He looks so cool. You sometimes to talk with him. You know that he owns a
         company, no girlfriends. But plenty of lovers. He never show his real heart. You do not like his character. But it is interesting 
         you two become friends. </string>
    <string name="editor_gaoye">He is a legendary figure in the editor region. He is so powerful to save a almost dead publisher. 
        You finally got a chance to talk with in a editor party. You successfully got this cell phone number. You will keep in touch. </string>
    <string name="editor_xiaoyesi">A new editor is assigned to your team. He is the son of another publisher owner. I have no idea why such a 
        heir need to come to your publisher. Anyway you find him working hard in a short time. You get along with him very well. Though he 
        does not express himself most of the time. But you think he is a good guy. </string>     
    <string name="editor_gaoyu">He takes the latest interview to you. You are the editor for him. You have seen several interview 
        from him. But this is the first time that you see him. He is full of power to the job. You are working get along with each other very well. </string>
    <string name="editor_lianjian"></string>
    <string name="editor_qiancun"></string>
    <string name="hooligan_majian"></string>
    <string name="hooligan_shidai"></string>
    <string name="hooligan_baimugui"></string>
    <string name="hooligan_longcheng"> </string>
    <string name="hooligan_shenwei"></string>
    <string name="lawyer_youchuan"> </string>
    <string name="lawyer_xiaoniaoyou"> </string>
    <string name="lawyer_baimugui"></string>
    <string name="lawyer_longcheng"></string>
    <string name="lawyer_hezhi"></string>
    <string name="manager_gaoye"></string>
    <string name="manager_hezhi"></string>
    <string name="manager_jiushi"></string>
    <string name="manager_guimu"> </string>
    <string name="manager_xiangle"> </string>
    <string name="noble_guimu"></string>
    <string name="noble_jiushi"> </string>
    <string name="noble_qiancun"> </string>
    <string name="noble_majian"></string>
    <string name="noble_shenwei"></string>
    <string name="police_baimugui"> </string>
    <string name="police_majian"></string>
    <string name="police_shidai"></string>
    <string name="police_longcheng"></string>
    <string name="police_shenwei"></string>   
    <string name="secretary_chenggu"></string>
    <string name="secretary_hezhi"></string>
    <string name="secretary_gaoye"></string>
    <string name="secretary_shouye"></string>
    <string name="secretary_xiangle"></string>
    <string name="star_shenghu"></string>
    <string name="star_quanshui"></string>
    <string name="star_xitiao"></string>
    <string name="star_yitiao"></string>
    <string name="star_gaoyu"></string>
    <string name="student_gaoyuan"></string>
    <string name="student_yuqi"></string>
    <string name="student_gaochuan"></string>
    <string name="student_xiaoniaoyou"></string>
    <string name="student_zhongsi"></string>
    <string name="teacher_gaoyuan"></string>
    <string name="teacher_yuqi"></string>
    <string name="teacher_lianjian"></string>
    <string name="teacher_qiancun"></string>
    <string name="teacher_zhongsi"></string>
    <string name="staff_heilai"></string>
    <string name="staff_shouye"></string>
    <string name="staff_longcheng"></string>
    <string name="staff_xiaoyesi"></string>
    <string name="staff_zhongsi"></string>
    <string name="writer_xiaoyesi"></string>
    <string name="writer_gaoye"></string>
    <string name="writer_shenghu"></string>
    <string name="writer_quanshui"></string>
    <string name="writer_yitiao"></string>
    <string name="you_know">You know </string>
    
    <!-- Change career -->
    <string name="change_career1">You decide to change your career from </string>
    <string name="change_career2"> to </string>
    <string name="change_career_title">Change Career</string>
    
    <!-- Move Forward -->
    <string name="move_forward1">You hit move forward. You move forward</string>
    <string name="move_forward2">steps.</string>
    <string name="move_forward_title">Move Forward</string>
    
    <!-- Move Back -->
    <string name="move_back1">You hit move back. You move back</string>
    <string name="move_back_title">Move Back</string>
</resources>
